<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1250"?>
<doc>
    <defaults>
        <defaultpage datatype="core" friendlyname="">index.pl</defaultpage>
        <currentdirectory></currentdirectory>
    </defaults>
    <metadata>
        <pagetitle datatype="property" friendlyname="Page title">My home</pagetitle>
        <linktext datatype="property" friendlyname="Page linktext">Home</linktext>
        <keywords datatype="property" friendlyname="Keyword list">desc</keywords>
        <description datatype="property" friendlyname="Page description">desc</description>
        <author datatype="property" friendlyname="Page author">desc</author>
    </metadata>
    <content>
        <body>Hello fellow foodies

I'm not a proffesionally chef, just a keen amateur but I really love cooking and am lucky to have friends who really love eating what I cook.

My mum, herself an excellent cook, taught me how to cook when I was little. Mum's style of cooking is both eccentric and traditional. She makes great meat and gravy based dishes, like stroganoff, beauf borgigone (I have no idea how to spell it!), hungarian goulash but her signature dish HAS to be her chicken and mushroom pie.  My mother has a skill for pastry which I've never managed duplicate - maybe when I'm older I'll develop the patience required!

I tend to make things up as I go along and fortunately, I normally like what I've made - I've only managed two utter disasters in my culinary adventures - one was a version of chicken satay that you could carve, the other was lard pizza!  I can also advise, never mix tahini with chicken - it's just not a good move.

Please feel free to use these recipes, pass them on, adjust them, mess them around - don't be afraid to experiment - what's the worst that can happen? You have to throw it away and get a pizza... and the best - you get the satisfaction of combining basic elements to create something really special.

Have fun.

Clare </body>
        <other>{CMS_ALTCONTENT}</other>
    </content>
</doc>
