<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1250"?>
<doc>
    <defaults>
        <defaultpage datatype="core" friendlyname="">index.pl</defaultpage>
    </defaults>
    <metadata>
        <pagetitle datatype="property" friendlyname="Page title">Sweet Chicken Pie</pagetitle>
        <linktext datatype="property" friendlyname="Page linktext">Sweet Chicken Pie</linktext>
        <keywords datatype="property" friendlyname="Keyword list">Sweet, Chicken, Pie, Dumplings</keywords>
        <description datatype="property" friendlyname="Page description">Sweet Chicken Pie</description>
        <author datatype="property" friendlyname="Page author">clare</author>
    </metadata>
    <content>
        <content1 datatype="text" friendlyname="Body"><P><STRONG>Sweet Chicken Pie</STRONG></P><P>Actually, it's Sweet Potato and chicken, and it's not a pie, it's a casserole with cheesey dumplings.&nbsp; This one's really good, especially as a proper winter warmer.</P><P><STRONG>Ingredients</STRONG></P><P>Half eaten left over roast chicken<BR>1 large onion<BR>2 sweet potatoes, peeled and chopped into 1" cubes<BR>2 tsps fennel seed<BR>1 tsp oregano<BR>1 tsp tarragon<BR>6 cloves of garlic rough chopped<BR>1/2 tsp hot curry powder<BR>1/2 tsp mustard powder<BR>2 chicken oxo cubes<BR>2 dessert spoons flour<BR>salt<BR>pepper</P><P><STRONG>For the dumplings<BR></STRONG>8 dessert spoons self raising flour<BR>4 dessert spoons atora veggie suet<BR>1/2 tsp mustard powder<BR>grated cheese to taste (so, a lot!)</P><P>Ok, rough chop the onions, wipe your eyes, blow your nose, then put them into a large wok with some olive oil (actually, just put the onions and the oil in the pan - leave out the snot and eyes).</P><P>Pop in a bit of butter and then add the tarragon, oregano and garlic.</P><P>Fry until the onion goes translucent then add the chicken - if you have any of the lovely jelly that coagulates at the bottom of cold roast chicken, pop that in too.</P><P>Give it a good old stir, then shove in the sweet spuds. Give a good stir (don't tickle it - stir it!).&nbsp; Keep it on high for about 5 minutes. </P><P>Now add the curry&nbsp;and mustard powder, stir, then the oxo cubes, stir, then the flour - guess what you do next?&nbsp;Yep, stir.&nbsp; Reduce the heat to medium.</P><P>Boil the kettle.&nbsp; Once the kettle's boiled, put the heat back up to high, and add the water gradually, stirring all the time to&nbsp;make a&nbsp;lovely thick chickeny sauce.&nbsp; Then add a bit more water to thin it out a bit, but not a lot.</P><P>Simmer the casserole for about 15 minutes, Then put in the oven on about 190-200C for 20 minutes.&nbsp;&nbsp;</P><P>In the meantime, make the dumplings by putting all the ingredients in a bowl and adding enough water to make a stiff dough.&nbsp; Roll into little balls.</P><P>After the casserole has been in for 20 minutes, take the lid off the casserole dish, stir the contents and put the dumplings on top - brush them with a little milk and put back in the over for another 20 minutes.</P><P>Serve with roast potatoes and veg boiled in butter!!!! Yum...</P></content1>
        
    </content>
</doc>
