<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1250"?>
<doc>
    <defaults>
        <defaultpage datatype="core" friendlyname="">index.pl</defaultpage>
    </defaults>
    <metadata>
        <pagetitle datatype="property" friendlyname="Page title">Yum Yum!</pagetitle>
        <linktext datatype="property" friendlyname="Page linktext">Yum Yum!</linktext>
        <keywords datatype="property" friendlyname="Keyword list">lamb, courgette, crispy, sweet potato, yum yum</keywords>
        <description datatype="property" friendlyname="Page description">Yum Yum!</description>
        <author datatype="property" friendlyname="Page author">clare</author>
    </metadata>
    <content>
        <content1 datatype="text" friendlyname="Body"><strong>Yum Yum!</strong><P>This is a true Belle classic... made up because I had minced lamb, spuds and courgettes that were about to go off and I didn't fancy mousakka...</P><P>Ingredients:</P><P>Minced lamb<BR>spuds (peeled and chopped by a willing victim - boyf or best mates are best for this - I hate peeling spuds!)<BR>courgettes<BR>tin of chopped toms<BR>half a pint of lamb stock - oxo of course<BR>2 tsp cinnamon<BR>2 tsp garlic chips (or fresh if you have it)<BR>1 tsp hot curry powder<BR>bayleaf<BR>pinch nutmeg<BR>3 cloves<BR>1 tsp sugar<BR>big bunch of coriander<BR>salt and pepper if you fancy it.</P><P>Can't quite remember how i did it... but basicly get your frying pan (I use a tefal red spot wok - they are the best - thanks mum!) or wok extra hot, pop in a splodge of flavoured olive oil mixed with a little regular sunflower oil (stops the olive oil from burning).  Shove in the lamb mince and stir fry for about 5 minutes - you want it kind of crispy in places and a good dark brown colour.  About 2 mins into the frying add your herbs and spices. Add the chopped courgettes and fry on a high heat for another 5 minutes.  If it starts to dry out (this is unlikely with lamb mince) add a splash of stock.  Add the chopped spuds - I haven't given quantities cos it's down to how many you've got or if you fancy spuds - I have a sneaking suspicion this dish would be nice with rice too.  Keept the dish moving, you want the heat to get the fat out of the lamb mince, and you want a bit of crispy but not burnt bits... get a nice bit of chargrill colour on the courgettes too.. yum.  The smell at this point should have your other half popping out of the living room to see what you're cooking - get him to open the wine / pour the vodka and coke and fetch your fags if you've left them in the living room.  Cook this lot together for around 10 minutes varying the heat so that it's still sizzling like crazy but isn't burning.  </P><P>Next add the tin of toms, a squidge of tom puree and a teaspoon of sugar to take the tartness out of the toms.  Cook this on the hob for a further 2 or 3 minutes - until the toms are settled into the dish.</P><P>Take a big old casserole dish - prefrably one you've pinched from your mum, pour the contents of the frying pan into the casserole dish - add as much stock as you think the spuds will absorb and cook in a hot oven until you've got a rich mix that's a nice consistency - should take about half an hour.</P><P>Serve with bread and lashings of butter.  Some sort of special bread would go nice with this too - maybe a chapati (I just couldn't be arsed to make them) or some naan (but I hate supermarket naan).</P><P>Silas and I couldn't decide what to call it, so it just became YUM YUM!  Any questions on this just email me... </P></content1>
        
    </content>
</doc>
