<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1250"?>
<doc>
    <defaults>
        <defaultpage datatype="core" friendlyname="">index.pl</defaultpage>
    </defaults>
    <metadata>
        <pagetitle datatype="property" friendlyname="Page title">Crispy Fish Cakes</pagetitle>
        <linktext datatype="property" friendlyname="Page linktext">Fish Cakes</linktext>
        <keywords datatype="property" friendlyname="Keyword list">fishcakes, fish, savouries, menu</keywords>
        <description datatype="property" friendlyname="Page description">Delicious fishcakes</description>
        <author datatype="property" friendlyname="Page author">midge</author>
    </metadata>
    <content>
        <content1 datatype="text" friendlyname="Body"><b>Crispy fishcakes</b>
<ul><li>5 handfuls of brown, granary breadcrumbs</li><li>2 salmon fillets</li><li>10 king prawns</li><li>1 courgette</li><li>1 medium sweet potato</li><li>2 medium white potatoes</li><li>1 large onion</li><li>large pinch nutmeg</li><li>3 cloves</li><li>2 bayleaves</li><li>1 pint milk</li><li>knob of butter</li><li>1 tablespoon of plain flour</li><li>2 eggs</li><li>juice of 1/2 lemon</li><li>salt</li><li>pepper</li><li>1 teaspoon of anchovy essence</li><li>2 handfuls of roughly chopped coriander</li></ul>
First wash the sweet and white potatoes, prick all over with a fork and microwave on high for 4 minutes. Then turn them over and microwave on high for another 4 minutes. If they are not soft to the touch, microwave until they are. Alternatively you can boil them, but they lose some of their flavour.

Finely chop the onions and caramelise in the butter for around 15 minutes.

Poach the salmon and prawns in the milk with nutmeg, cloves and bayleaves. Bring to the boil, then simmer for around 8 minutes. If the prawns were pre-cooked (pink) they do not need poaching with the salmon. Remove the salmon and prawns from the milk and discard the cooking liquor with the cloves and garlic.

Allow the potatoes, onions and fish to cool. Grate the courgette. Wrap in teatowel and squeeze out all the excess water.

Flake the cooled salmon into a large mixing bowl. Roughly chop the prawns and add to the bowl. Cut the potatoes in half and spoon out the soft middles, then add to the fish along with the coriander, 2 handfuls of the breadcrumbs, grated courgette and caramelised onion.

Add salt and pepper, lemon juice and the anchovy essence, then combine together with a small wooden spoon.

Take three shallow dishes. Put teh flour in the first bowl, the beaten eggs in the second and the rest of the breadcrumbs in the third.

Take a small handful of the mixture and form into a ball andthen flatten until it is around an inch thick. (quick tip: coat your hands thoroughly with the flour first, to stop the mixture sticking). If your mixture is not 'wet' enough to bind, add a little of the egg mixture. Dip the fishcakes first in the flour, then the egg and then into the breadcrumbs until it's covered all over. Place the fishcake onto a greased baking tray. Repeat this until you've run out of mixture and bake in an oven at 220<sup>0</sup>C for 25 minutes.</content1>
        <content2 datatype="text" friendlyname="Right content">{CMS_CONTENT2}</content2>
        <content3 datatype="image" friendlyname="Right hand image">{CMS_CONTENT3}</content3>
        <content4 datatype="image" friendlyname="Content title image">{CMS_CONTENT4}</content4>

    </content>
</doc>
