<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1250"?>
<doc>
    <defaults>
        <defaultpage datatype="core" friendlyname="">index.pl</defaultpage>
    </defaults>
    <metadata>
        <pagetitle datatype="property" friendlyname="Page title">Possibly the best Fish Pie in the World</pagetitle>
        <linktext datatype="property" friendlyname="Page linktext">Fish Pie</linktext>
        <keywords datatype="property" friendlyname="Keyword list">fish, pie, recipe, Possibly the best Fish Pie in the World,</keywords>
        <description datatype="property" friendlyname="Page description">Possibly the best Fish Pie in the World</description>
        <author datatype="property" friendlyname="Page author">MIJE</author>
    </metadata>
    <content>
        <content1 datatype="text" friendlyname="Body">Possibly the best Fish Pie in the World

This recipe is a mixture of three recipes by Rick Stien, the two fat ladies and my mum!  This is a special occasion pie, it's not for those on a diet.

Ingredients:

8oz raw tiger prawns
8oz organic salmon
8oz coley fillet
1 large onion, very finely diced
2 bay leaves
2 cloves
1 tsp fresh chopped thyme
1/2 tsp dries parsley
1 tsp english mustard powder
2 tsp anchovy essence
large pinch of fresh grated nutmeg
lots of unsalted butter
1/2 pint double cream
1/2 pint milk
as many hard boiled eggs as you fancy
3oz gruyére cheese
1oz parmesan cheese
3lb boiled potatoes 

Poach the fish in the milk and 3/4 of the cream. Also add the bay leaves, cloves and nutmeg.  Poach gently for 6 minutes, then add the prawns. Poach for another 30 seconds and then stain, keeping the liquor. Strain the liquor and put to one side. 

Melt the butter into a good non-stick pan over a medium heat.  Add the onion and garlic and cook very gently for 10-12 minutes until the onion has softened and gone translucent. Stir in the flour to form a wet roux and cook for a further two minutes. Very gradually, add the poaching liquor, stirring continuously. Once all the juice has been added, cook over an extremely low heat for a further 10 minutes. 

Add the anchovy essence, herbs and mustard powder. Stir in well. Flake the fish making sure there are no bones or skin. Try to keep the flakes fairly chunky. Add the fish to the pan, fold in gently and then add a little salt and pepper to taste - you shouldn't need much. Remove from the heat.

Take the boiled potatoes, fresh from the pan.  Add double cream, butter, salt and pepper and mash thoroughly until you have smooth, lump free mash. Stir in half the cheese.

Take an oven proof dish. Put the fish mixture in the bottom. Peel and halve the hard boiled eggs. Place them on top of the fix mixture and then place the cheesey mash on top of them. The put cheese on top.

Place in a medium to hot oven for 30 minutes, until the cheese is golden.

Serve with fresh crusty bread and green beans. Goes well with a nice chilled Pinot Grigio.

Enjoy fish pie sensibly!
This is EXTREMELY easy to over-eat... and because of the mash, eating to much of this hurts for quite a while... my friends and family have all experienced the pain that comes of bingeing on fish pie!

</content1>
        
    </content>
</doc>
